Spiros Xiarchos

Network Engineer

Email: sp@xiarchos.gr Web: sp.xiarchos.gr

About Me

Hey there, I'm Spiros and I am an undergraduate student in the Department of Informatics of the Ionian University.

My interests include, but are not limited to, gaining experience in the following areas:

- Networking (Firewalling, SDWAN)
- Web development (e.g. React or Angular)
- E-shop Frameworks (e.g. WooCommerce or Magento)
- Mobile development (iOS only)
- · End-to-end testing suites (e.g. puppeteer)

Technical skills are not the only area I have developed through my experience. My peers describe me as a valuable team member, who knows how to work under strict deadlines and provide quality results.

Education

B.Sc. Informatics

Ionian University Corfu GR

01/10/2015 - Present

Specialization in Information Systems.

Main courses follow:

- Electronic Commerce/Information Systems and Supply Management
- Analysis and Design of Information Systems/Strategic Management of Information Systems
- Software Application, Communications and Network Security/Information Systems Security Management
- Information Privacy Policies and EnhancingTechnologies/Social and Legal Issues of ICTs

Experience

Network Administrator

Intercompass MPD Glyfada GR 01/06/2022 - Present

- Network Design, Deployment and Administration (Mikrotik/Cisco).
- System Operations Assitant (WHM CPanel /Direct Admin/Microsoft 365 /Proxmox/Synology/NextCLoud /OSTicket System/SnipelT).

Network Management Customer Support

NET7, Corfu GR 01/10/2015 - Present

- WISP Network Manager (Ubiquiti / Mikrotik)
- Customer Support Manager (UISP CRM)

Network Management IT Support

Messinian Networks 23/06/2016 - 30/11/2022

- 23/06/2016 31/08/2016:
 Training on Network Installations and IT Support (Kalamata). (Mikrotik/ Ubiquiti)
- 01/09/2016 20/06/2021:
 B2B IT Support and Network Management (Corfu). (Mikrotik/Synology/ VMware)
- 21/06/2021 30/11/2022: Network

 Management and Customer Support Service
 (Kalamata). (UISP CRM/NMS) (Hybrid)

Little More About Me

Apart from my job's related interests I'm keen on:

- Traveling
- Audiophilism and Vinyl Records
- Motor Sports